Adventure of a Lifetime
Turn your magic on
Umi she'd say
Everything you want's a dream away
And we are legends every day
That's what she told me
Turn your magic on to me she'd say
Everything you want's a dream away
Under this pressure
Under this weight we are diamonds
Now I feel my heart beating
I feel my heart underneath my skin
But I feel my heart beating oh you make me feel
Like I'm alive again
Alive again
Oh you make me feel like
I'm alive again
Said I can't go on not in this way
I'm a dream that died by light of day
Gonna hold up half the sky and say only
I own me
And I feel my heart beating
I can feel my heart underneath my skin
Oh I can feel my heart beating 'cos you make me feel like
I'm alive again
Alive again
Oh you make me feel like
I'm alive again
Turn your magic on
Umi she'd say
Everything you want's a dream away
Under this pressure
Under this weight
We are diamonds taking shape
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
If we've only got this life this adventure oh then
I And if we've only got this life you get me through
And if we've only got this life in this adventure oh then
I want to share it with you with you
With you
Yes with you
Yes I do ooh
Ooh ooh